Vernon Greene Papers
Vernon Greene Papers
- Reference files
  - Hospital-News, 1934; 1946,; 1955-1958,; 1960-1962,; undated; photos, clippings, published material, sketches, letter from the Red Cross, NCS, writings (Box 28)
    Hospital, Humor, Ideas, Illustrations (Johnstone and Cushing promotional material), Inspiration, Japan Society, Kingman, Don, Kuekes, Edward (signed promotional material), Labor (photos, sketches), Leigh, W. Colston- Bureau of Lectures and Entertainment (correspondence), Lincoln School PTO, Living Library, Men Smiling (sketch), Metro Sunday Comics- Readership of Editorial Comics, Models from All Angles, Moods (sketch), Music, New York (photos), News Pictures (of Greene)
  - Nudism-Press Photographers' Association of New York, 1932-1933; 1936-1939,; 1946,; 1952,; 1957,; 1960-1964,; undated; photos, published and printed material, clippings, correspondence, sketches (Box 29)
    Nudism, Office, Ohio University (correspondence and printed material), Ohio and Columbia University, Orient, Parades, Past Interviews-WRVR, Pearl Harbor, Portland Symphony Ball Manhattan West, Portraits, Press Photographers' Association of New York
  - Production Ideas-Sports (Track), 1930; 1932-1933,; 1938-1939,; 1945-1946,; 1949,; 1954-1956,; 1962-1964,; undated; sketches, typed material, clippings, photos, catalogs (Box 30)
    Production of Ideas for A.G.I. Variety Show, Publicity, Rusty- All the Family, RCA at the World's Fair, Regional Members, Riverside Church, Scouts, Ships (photos), Smiling, Smoking, Social Problems, Sports (General), Sports (Baseball), Sports (Boxing and Wrestling), Sports (Football), Sports (Track)
  - Stadiums-World War II, 1930; 1932-1933,; 1935-1936,; 1938-1939,; 1941,; 1951-1952,; 1961,; 1963-1964; undated; photos, sketches, clippings, printed material, correspondence (Box 31)
    Stadiums, Statues, Sudden Exit Fire, Telephones, Television and Radio, United Nations- U.S. Committee for UNICEF, War (Army, Navy), War (Korea), War (World War II)
  - Woman's-Young, 1950; 1961-1964,; undated; correspondence, Woman Bowler magazine, printed material, sketches, clippings, photographs (Box 15)
    Woman's International Bowling Congress, Inc., World Federalists, Wyckoff politics, Young, Loretta
- Works by Greene
  - Drawings, sketches and paintings
    - At the Circus, undated (Oversize 7)
    - Color paintings and drawings, undated (Oversize 32)
    - Extra large drawings and sketches, Undated; marker, pencil, some crayon, several are smaller, maybe likely done during live cartooning performances; 36 items 40" x 40" (Mapcase 1, Drawer 100)
    - Figure sketches, undated (Oversize 32)
    - Life sketches, undated (Box 12)
    - Paintings, Aug 24 1931; undated; 2 items; includes a painting of Lake Louise (Box 12)
    - The Red Cardinal, undated (Oversize 6)
    - Sketchbooks and drawings, Undated (Oversize 6)
    - Sketches, undated; 2 folders (Oversize 6)
    - Sketches, undated (Oversize 7)
    - Sketches, undated (Box 12)
    - Sketchbooks and drawings, undated (Box 12)
    - Sketchpad, Undated (Oversize 32)
  - Comics and cartoons
    - Beatrice Fairfax
      - Captions, undated (Oversize 8)
      - Comic books, 1950-1951; 4 items (Box 32)
      - Drawings and sketches, undated (Oversize 8)
      - Photographs, undated; 2 folders (Oversize 8)
      - Proofs, undated (Oversize 8)
      - Proofs, 1940s; primarily reverse negative proofs; also 2 positive proofs; 64 items (Oversize 15)
    - Bible Bee
      - Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 17)
      - Clippings, 1947; 1950,; undated (Box 17)
      - Drawings, undated (Box 17)
      - Photographs, undated (Box 17)
      - Proofs, 1947-1951; undated; 3 folders (Box 17)
      - Publicity, 1947; undated (Box 17)
      - Research material, 1940s; undated (Box 17)
      - Title Proofs, undated (Box 17)
    - Bringing Up Father, Some material likely produced by George McManus. See George McManus work in the Works by Others series.
      - Artwork, 1949; 1952,; 1958,; undated (Oversize 29)
      - Captions, 1947-1960; undated (Box 18)
      - Clippings (color Sunday), 1933; 1935-1944,; 1947,; 1949-1956 (Oversize 4)
      - Clippings about the strip, 1960-1963; undated (Box 18)
      - Drawings and sketches, undated (Box 18)
      - Foreign language clippings (color), 1952; 1954-1955,; undated (Oversize 29)
      - Proofs (daily and Sunday), 1955-1958 (Oversize 2)
      - Proofs (daily and Sunday), 1959-1963; 1964 Jan-Oct (Oversize 3)
      - Proofs (daily), 1961 Sep; 1 sheet (Box 15)
      - Proofs, 1957-1964 (Box 47)
      - Proofs by subject, 1954-1963
        - Accidents-Autos (Box 41)
        - Backviews-Butlers (Box 41)
        - Carrying-Cats (Box 41)
        - Characters-Cooking (Box 41)
        - Cops-Crying (Box 41)
        - Dance-Dinty (Box 41)
        - Dishes-Dressing (Box 41)
        - Eating-Fur Coats (Box 41)
        - Gambling-Groups (Box 41)
        - Hair-Knitting (Box 42)
        - Laborers-Music (Box 42)
        - Laborers-Music (Box 42)
        - Negligee-Peering (Box 42)
        - Phones-Pushing (Box 42)
        - Rain-Running (Box 42)
        - Safes-Sitting (Box 42)
        - Slacks-Swimming Pool (Box 43)
        - Takes-Visiting (Box 43)
        - Waiting-Writing (Box 43)
      - Promotional Material, 1950s (Box 15)
      - Slides and negatives, undated (Box 18)
    - Charlie the Conscript
      - Clippings, 1941-1943 (Box 18)
      - Drawings and sketches, undated (Box 18)
    - Cherry and the Colonel
      - Original artwork, undated (Oversize 29)
        Gift of Karl H. Schadow, 2013.
    - Little Phil Ossifer
      - Clippings and miscellaneous, 1949-1950; undated; from the General View, newspaper of Columbia University (Box 19)
    - Love and Marriage
      - Clippings, 1935 (Box 19)
    - Mac the Medic
      - Clippings, 1943 (Box 19)
    - Mickey McDougal
      - Clippings and proofs, 1937 (Box 19)
    - Perry Mason
      - Drawings and sketches, undated; 3 items (Oversize 29)
      - Proofs and negatives, undated; 41 items (Oversize 29)
    - The Shadow
      - Assignment and note from Street & Smith, 1940 (Box 19)
      - Captions, undated (Box 19)
      - Clippings (comic strips), undated (Oversize 28)
      - Drawings and sketches, undated; includes one engraver's mat (Box 19)
      - Proofs
      - Proofs, 1940s
      - Proofs for comic book, undated (Oversize 28)
      - Proofs for comic strip (daily), 1940s; 169 sheets (Oversize 28)
      - Proofs for comic strip, 1940s; miscellaneous (Oversize 28)
      - Publicity, 1940s (Oversize 28)
      - Research material, undated (Box 19)
      - Scripts, xxxxx scripts for The Shadow can be located in the Street and Smith xxxx. The listing below are scripts that were located in the Vernon Greene Papers
        Assignment with Murder
        Dragon’s Tongue Murders
        The Hoodoo Shop
        The Devil’s Hour
        The Terror by Night
        The Organ Played at Midnight
        The Case of the Priceless Pompano
      - Shadow Magazine covers, 1939-1940 (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Memories of Blue and Gold, containing "Bringing Up Father" cartoon, 1964; high school yearbook for Dillsboro High School, includes cartoon drawn by Greene for the yearbook staff (p. 48) (Box 19)
      - Printed material, Nov 1942; 1950,; undated; Issue of U.S. Camera, The Little Red Book and Bible Game (Oversize 24)
      - Proofs, undated; negative proofs, some only partial, some with circus theme, appear to be for Street and Smith Trail Blazers Comics, unsure if all are by Greene,; 5 items (Oversize 24)
      - Proofs, undated (Oversize 29)
  - Commercial art
    - Chesebrough Manufacturing Co- Rusty and Dusty, 1949-1951; color proofs (Oversize 29)
    - Chiclets, undated; drawings and proofs (Box 19)
    - Dentyne chewing gum, undated; proofs and promotional material (Oversize 28)
    - Dick's Adventures in Defense of New York, 1951; correspondence and proofs (Box 19)
    - Eddy and Teddy, the Scout Twins, undated; drawings and proofs (Box 19)
    - Shower Fun, undated; photographs and clippings (Box 19)
    - USAF Recruiting Service Commander's program, 1961; illustrated by Greene (Box 19)
  - Newspaper illustrations, editorial and sports cartoons
    - Clipping from Kuryer Codzienny (Polish Daily Courier), Nov 11 1937 (Box 18)
    - Clippings, 1936-1944; 1961 (Box 18)
    - Engraver's mats, undated; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - Proofs by date, 1933-1942 (Box 18)
    - Proofs by caption, undated (Box 18)
    - Portraits (proofs), undated; includes sports figures (Box 18)
    - "Board of Trade", proof for editorial cartoon (Box 19)
    - "Expansion and Subtraction", undated; artwork for the Daily Mirror (Oversize 29)
    - "Love's Litany", 1935; proofs for serialized story illustrated by Greene; 13 items (Oversize 28)
    - Nudism in Chicago illustration, Jul 1933; proof for article on nudism in Chicago, illustrated by Green (Box 19)
    - Ojibway article engraving plate and clipping, circa 1932 (Box 19)
  - Recordings, audiotapes
    - Speeches
      - #46 Korea, undated (Box 45)
      - #47 Drawing Children and miscellaneous radio, music and talk, undated
      - #48 Vernon Greene- interview for Children's World- tells of his life and work, undated (Box 45)
      - #49 Untitled, 1960 (Box 45)
      - #50 Untitled / Group Therapy WBAM Macbeth, undated (Box 45)
    - Radio and television
      - #42 "Can Comics Change our Culture", 1963; includes correspondence (Box 46)
      - The Cartoonist's Art WRVR, WAMU, 1961-1964; correspondence and printed material (Box 46)
      - #43 Cartoonists at Large, undated; television show hosted by Greene (Box 45)
      - #44 and #45 History of Comics, undated; includes a set of slides (Box 45)
      - #36 Interview on CBS News, Vernon Greene and daughter Bonnie, 1962 (Box 45)
      - #37 Interview on CFPL TV, 1961 (Box 45)
      - #38 Interview with Far East Network, U.S. Army Element, 1957; includes correspondence (Box 46)
      - #39 Interview on "Monitor"- NBC Radio, 1959; includes correspondence (Box 46)
      - #40 Interview on the "Today" show, 1963 (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous
      - #41 Phone conversation with Charles Schulz in California, undated (Box 45)
  - Scrapbooks
    - Scrapbook, 1932-1942; due to its condition, the scrapbook has been taken apart and most items have been removed from their pages and foldered; editorial cartoons (Box 15)
    - Scrapbook, 1940s-1950s (Oversize 31)
    - Scrapbooks, 1932-1934; due to its condition, one scrapbook has been taken apart and most items have been removed from their pages and foldered; 2 items; editorial and sports cartoons (Oversize 30)
- Works by others
  - All in the Family by R.M. Brinkerhoff
    - Proofs (color), Feb 2 1935 (Oversize 15)
  - Ambassador by Otto Soglow
    - Clippings (color Sunday), 1933; 1 item (Oversize 20)
  - America's Greatest Comic Weekly
    - Clippings (color Sunday), 1936-1941; complete and incomplete newspaper comics sections (Oversize 9)
  - Ayer Lane by Dale Ulrey
    - Proofs (daily), 1947 Apr; 2 sheets (Oversize 29)
  - Barney Google by Billy DeBeck
    - Proofs (daily), 1935-1937 (Oversize 21)
    - Proofs (Sunday), Nov-Dec 1935; Jan 1936,; Mar-Sep 1936 (Oversize 21)
  - Ben Webster's Page by Edwin Alger
    - Proofs (color Sunday), Feb 2 1935; Feb 24 1935,; Mar 3 1935 (Oversize 18)
  - Berry's Babes by Michael Berry
    - Proofs, clippings, postcards, 1956 (Box 13)
  - Bible Stories by Dan Smith
    - Proofs, 1934 (Oversize 26)
  - Billy Make Believe by H. Homan
    - Proofs (color), 1935 (Oversize 18)
  - Bozo by Foxo Reardon
    - Proofs (daily), 1947 May; 2 sheets (Oversize 29)
  - Brenda Starr Reporter by Dale Messick
    - Proofs (color Sunday), Feb 7 1954; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Brick Bradford by William Ritt and Clarence Gray
    - Proofs (daily), 1933 Aug-Oct; 1934 Jan,; 1934 Apr-May,; 1948 Jul-Aug (Oversize 19)
    - Proofs (promotional material), 1933; announcing start of the strip; 2 items (Oversize 19)
    - Proofs (Sunday), 1948 Mar-Aug; 24 items (Oversize 19)
    - Tearsheets (color Sunday), 1935 Feb; 1935 Sep,; 1935 Nov-Dec,; 1936 Jan-1938 Jan (Oversize 11)
  - Bringing Up Father by George McManus
    - Proofs (daily and Sunday), 1938; 1941-1943,; 1952 Nov-Dec,; 1953 Aug-Sep,; 1954 Jan-Dec; 4 folders; includes 2 color proofs (Oversize 32)
    - Proofs (daily and Sunday), 1935-1938; 1940 Mar-Dec,; 1941 Jan-Dec,; 1943 Dec,; 1944,; 1946 Jan-1948 Jan,; 1948 Nov,; 1949 Jun-Dec,; 1950 Jan-Aug; 13 folders (Oversize 1)
    - Proofs (daily), 1946; 1954,; 1964 (Box 47)
      Proofs from 1964 also include work by Bill Kavanagh.
    - Proofs (daily), 1948-1954; 1965,; 1966 (Oversize 34)
      Proofs also include work from Greene, Bill Kavanagh, Hal "Camp" Campagna and Frank Fletcher.
  - Broncho Bill by Harry O'Neill
    - Proofs (color), Feb 2 1935; 1 item (Oversize 10)
    - Tearsheets (color), 1935 Feb; 1935 Jul-Aug,; 1935 Nov,; 1936 Mar-Jun; 11 items (Oversize 11)
  - Brutus by Johnny Gruelle
    - Clippings (color), 1935-1938 (Oversize 11)
      1935- Oct 13, Nov 17
      1936- Mar 22, Apr 5, Jun 14, Jul 12, 26, Aug 2, 16, Sep 6, Nov 8, 15, 22, Dec 6, 13
      1937- Jan 31, Feb 7, Apr 18, May 2, 9, 16, 25, 30 Jun 6, 13, 20, 27, Jul 11, 25, Aug 1, 22, Sep 5, 12, 17, Oct 3, 10, 17, 31, Nov 28, Dec 5
      1938- Jan 9, 13
  - Bungle Family by H.J. Tuthill
    - Clippings (color Sunday), 1935 Jun; 1936 Feb,; 1937 Feb-Jun,; 1937 Oct-Nov,; 1938 Jan; 19 items (Oversize 20)
  - Buzz Sawyer and Buzz Sawyer's Pal Sweeney by Roy Crane
    - Proofs, 1948 Mar-Dec; 40 items (Oversize 18)
    - Proofs (daily), 1948 (Oversize 27)
    - Sketches, undated (Oversize 27)
  - "Cap" Stubbs and Tippie by Edwina (Dumm)
    - Proofs (daily), circa 1930s; 18 items (Oversize 19)
  - Chicago Tribune New York News syndicate
    - Proofs of promotional material, 1933-1934; undated; some color (Oversize 29)
  - Countess and the Cowboy, Carolyn's Cadet and Vacation Varieties of 1936 by Russell Patterson
    - Clippings (color), Sep 11 1932; Jan 22 1933,; 1936; newspaper feature and serialized stories (Oversize 19)
  - Crack-Ups by Ed Nofziger
    - Proofs (daily), 1947 Apr; 2 sheets (Oversize 29)
  - Curly Harper by Lyman Young
    - Proofs (Sunday), 1934-1938; 47 items (Oversize 19)
  - Cuties by E. Simms Campbell
    - Proofs (daily), May 13-25 1940; Jun 3-8 1940,; Feb7-12 1955; 4 sheets (Oversize 24)
  - Dan Flagg by Don Sherwood
    - Sample book (color), 1963 (Oversize 10)
  - Detroit Sunday Mirror Comic Section
    - Full sections, 1931 Oct-Dec; 1932 Feb-May,; Jun 4 1932,; Aug 6 1932; many are incomplete (Oversize 16)
  - Dick Tracy by Chester Gould
    - Clippings (color Sunday), 1935; 1936 Nov-Dec,; 1937 Jan-May,; 1937 Sep-Dec; 1938 Jan-Feb,; 1939 Oct,; 1939 Dec,; 1940 Apr,; 1948 Jul; 39 items (Oversize 11)
  - Dick's Adventures in Dreamland by Neil O'Keefe and Max Trell
    - Proofs (color Sunday), 1951 Feb-May; 9 items (Oversize 23)
    - Proofs (Sunday), 1947-1950; 4 folders (Oversize 27)
  - Dingelhoofer und His Dog by J. Knerr
    - Clippings (color Sunday), 1936 Jul; 1936 Nov-Dec,; 1937 Jan-Apr,; 1937 Jun-Jul,; 1937 Sep-Nov,; 1938 Jan; 32 items (Oversize 20)
  - Dixie Dugan by J.P. McEvoy and J.H. Striebel
    - Proofs (color Sunday), 1935 Feb-Mar; 9 items (Oversize 18)
  - Doctor Bill by Jack Tippit
    - Proofs, 1960; 1 sheet (Oversize 29)
  - Dr. Bobbs by Elliot and McArdle
    - Proofs (daily), 1941 Nov-1942 Feb; 16 items (Oversize 16)
  - Drift Marlo by I. M. Levitt, Phil Evans and Tom Cooke
    - Promotional material, undated; 1 item (Oversize 23)
  - Editorial cartoons
    - Proofs of Chamberlain, 1935-1937; 51 sheets (Oversize 24)
    - Proofs of Wud, 1935-1936; King Features Syndicate; 53 sheets (Oversize 24)
    - Clippings, circa 1930s-1950s; Carlisle, Corley, Herblock, Hutton, Kelen, Messner, Shoemaker (Box 13)
  - Ella Cinders by Bill Conselman and Charlie Plumb
    - Tearsheets (color Sunday), Dec 10 1935; Jul 26 1936,; Aug 2 1936,; Aug 16 1936,; Aug 15 1937; 5 items (Oversize 11)
  - Etta Kett by Paul Robinson, 1935 items also contain Robinson's The Love Birds.
    - Proofs and tearsheets, 1933 Jan; 1936; daily proofs, color Sunday tearsheets; 4 sheets (Oversize 11)
    - Tearsheets (color Sunday), 1935 Feb; 1935 Oct,; 1936 Feb-May,; 1936 Jul-Dec,; 1937 Apr-May,; 1937 Sep,; 1937 Nov,; 1938 Mar,; 1938 Aug (Oversize 11)
  - Flash Gordon by Dan Barry
    - Proofs (daily), Sep 4-9 1961; 1 sheet (Oversize 16)
  - Gabby by Joe King and William Ritt
    - Proofs (daily), 1935 Sep-Oct; 2 sheets (Oversize 22)
  - Gags and Gals by Jefferson Machamer
    - Clippings (color), Nov 7 1937; 1 item (Oversize 20)
    - Proofs, 1936; 1 item (Oversize 10)
  - Gasoline Alley by Frank King
    - Proofs (color Sunday), Feb 7 1954; 1 item (Box 13)
    - Tearsheets, 1936-1937; 96 items (Oversize 16)
  - Glamour Girls by Don Flowers
    - Pencil sketch, undated; 1 item (Oversize 18)
    - Proofs (daily), Jan 10-Feb 12 1955; 1953 Jan,; 1953 May-1954 Dec; 75 sheets (Oversize 18)
    - Proofs (Sunday), Sep 5 1948; Sep 12 1948,; 1949 Jul-Oct,; Jul 15 1951,; Feb 24 1952,; Dec 27 1953; 18 items (Oversize 18)
  - Grandma by Harris
    - Promotional material, 1947; 3 items (Oversize 29)
  - Harold Teen by Carl Ed
    - Proofs (color Sunday), Feb 14 1954; Feb 21 1954,; Feb 28 1954; 3 items (Box 13)
    - Tearsheets, 1936-1938; 92 items (Oversize 16)
  - Hejji by Dr. Suess
    - Proofs (color Sunday), Apr 21-Jun 23 1935; 10 items (Oversize 18)
  - Heart of Juliet Jones by Stan Drake
    - Proofs (daily), 1953-1954; 1961; 52 sheets (Oversize 19)
    - Proofs (color Sunday), Dec 16 1962; Dec 30 1962,; Jan 6 1963,; Jan 27 1963,; Jul 14 1963 (Oversize 19)
  - Henry by Carl Anderson
    - Tearsheets (color Sunday), 1935 Jul-Aug; 1935 Oct-Dec,; 1936 Feb-Oct,; 1937 Jan-Mar,; 1938 Oct-Feb (Oversize 11)
  - Holly of Hollywood by Pop Momand
    - Proofs (color Sunday), 1935; 8 items (Oversize 18)
      Feb 3, 10, 17
      Mar 3, 10, 17, 24, 31
  - Home Sweet Home by Jack Callahan
    - Tearsheets (color Sunday), 1935-1938; majority are numbered (Oversize 12)
  - Hopalong Cassidy by Dan Spiegle
    - Proofs (Sunday), 1951 May-Nov; 25 items (Oversize 18)
  - Illustrations by Hammon
    - Proofs, circa 1930s; appeared with serialized stories distributed by King Features Syndicate including More Money, Czarina's Rubies, Knave's Girl, Cast Into Eden, Caroline; 105 sheets (Oversize 21)
  - Inspector Wade by Edgar Wallace
    - Proofs (daily), 1938 Jun-Oct 1; 1940 Apr; 18 sheets (Oversize 21)
  - Jeanie by Selma Diamond and Gill Fox
    - Original artwork, Mar 3 1952; Mar 7 1952; 2 items (Oversize 24)
  - Jane Arden by Monte Barrett and Russell E. Ross
    - Proofs (color Sunday), Feb 10-Mar 3 1935; Apr 8 1935; 5 items (Oversize 18)
  - Judge cartoons
    - Clippings, 1923-1930; 4 folders; Harry Grant Dart, Charles Forbell, R.B. Fuller, covers by John Held Jr. and other miscellaneous cartoonists (Box 13)
  - Kass Nova and Mox Nix by Jim Malone
    - Artwork, undated (Map-case 1, Drawer 100)
  - Life magazine
    - Clippings of comic strips and magazine covers, 1922-1931; 3 folders; work of W. Heath Robinson, John Held Jr. and other miscellaneous cartoonists (Box 13)
  - Miss Chuckie by Yukio Sugiura
    - Comic strip (printed material), 1961; printed on rice paper (Oversize 29)
  - New York Journal American
    - Saturday evening comics section, Nov 3 1935; Mar 12 1938,; Mar 19 1938; 3 items (Oversize 11)
  - Newspaper illustrations by Nell Brinkley
    - Clippings and proofs, 1935; 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Kid Sister/Tim Tyler's Luck by Lyman Young
    - Proofs (Sunday), 1934; 13 items (Oversize 19)
      Feb 4, 11, 18
      Mar 11, 18
      Apr 1, 8, 15, 22, 29
      May 6, 13, 27
  - King Features Syndicate Comics Page
    - Proofs, 1933, 1935-1936, 1939, 1941
  - Krazy Kat by George Herriman
    - Proofs (daily), 1936 Jul-Sep; 12 sheets (Oversize 21)
    - Tearsheets (color Sunday), 1936 May; 1936 Sep-Nov,; 1937 Jan,; 1937 Jun,; 1937 Sep-Oct (Oversize 12)
  - Little Joe by Leffingwell
    - Tearsheets (color Sunday), Feb 28 1937; Apr 4 1937,; Feb 6 1938; 3 items (Oversize 11)
  - Little King by Otto Soglow
    - Clippings, 1936-1938; 33 items (Oversize 20)
  - Little Miss Muffet by Fanny Y. Cory
    - Pencil drawing, undated; 1 item (Oversize 19)
    - Proofs, 1936; 1947 Nov-1948 May,; 1948 Jul; 32 items (Oversize 19)
  - Little Nemo in Slumberland by Windsor McKay
    - Promotional Material, 1947; from the Richardson Feature Syndicate announcing the availability of Little Nemo starting March 2, 1937, features 4 color strips; 1 item (Oversize 18)
  - Little Orphan Annie by Harold Gray
    - Clippings (color Sunday), 1935-1938 (Oversize 12)
    - Proofs (color Sunday), Jan 31 1954; Feb 28 1954; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Lone Ranger by Fran Striker
    - Proofs, 1948 Jan-Aug; 1951 Jun-Nov; 56 items (Oversize 10)
  - Lovebyrds
    - Clippings, 1935-1937
  - Magnificent Hoax by E. Phillips Oppenheim and Mathieu
    - Proofs, 1935; serialized story; 9 items (Oversize 19)
  - Mandrake the Magician by Lee Felk
    - Proofs (daily), 1935-1936; 1939-1940; 34 sheets (Oversize 21)
    - Proofs (Sunday), 1935 Mar-Dec; 1936 Jan-Apr,; 1951 Jun-Oct; 64 items (Oversize 21)
  - Merry Menagerie by Walt Disney
    - Proofs (daily), 1954 Jan-Nov; 50 sheets (Oversize B2)
  - Mickey Finn by Lank Leonard
    - Proofs (daily), 1960 (Oversize 29)
  - Moon Mullins by Frank Willard
    - Proofs (color Sunday), Feb 14 1954; Feb 21 1954; 2 items (Box 13)
    - Tearsheets (color Sunday), 1935-1938; 1940,; 1951-1954; 103 items (Oversize 16)
  - Mr. and Mrs. by Arthur Falwell and King Pratt
    - Clippings, 1933; 1935-1938; 77 items (Oversize 20)
  - Mutt and Jeff by Al Smith
    - Proofs (color Sunday), 1961; May 31 1964; 2 items (Oversize 23)
  - Nancy by Ernie Bushmiller
    - Proofs (for Periquita), Nov 25 1956; Dec 30 1956,; Feb 3 1957,; Feb 17 1957,; Feb 24 1957,; Mar 17 1957,; Mar 24 1957,; May 26 1957,; Jul 7 1957 (Box 13)
    - Proofs (Sunday), Mar-Jul 1955; 15 items (Box 13)
    - Sketches, undated (Box 13)
  - Newspaper Enterprise Association (NEA) Comic Page
    - Proofs, Sep-Nov 1953 (Oversize 19)
  - NEA Service Weekly
    - Proofs, 1953 Jul-Oct (Oversize 10)
  - (New Adventures of) Flossy Frills by Carolyn Wells and Russell Patterson
    - Clippings (color), 1939-1942; 12 items (Oversize 20)
      1939: Nov 12, 26; Dec 3
      1940: Jan 7, 14, 21
      1941: Feb 9; Mar 2, 9
      1942: May 3, 10, 31
  - On Our Block by Jack Welch
    - Proofs (daily), 1937; 1938 Jan,; 22 sheets (Oversize 21)
  - Oregonian Comics
    - Clippings (color Sunday), 1941 Jun-Aug; 10 items (Oversize 20)
  - Our Bill by Harry Haenigsen
    - Clippings, 1948; 1950-1954; 9 items (Oversize 12)
  - Out of the Ink Well by Max Fleischer
    - Proofs (color Sunday), Nov 25 1934; Dec 1 1934,; Dec 15 1934 (Oversize 18)
  - Out Our Way by J.R. Williams
    - Clippings, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Pa's Son-in-Law by Wellington
    - Clippings (color), Nov 1933; 1937 Sep-Nov; 6 items (Oversize 20)
  - Peanuts (Carlitos) by Charles M. Schulz
    - Proofs (Sunday), Jul 7 1957; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Penny by Harry Haenigsen
    - Clippings (color Sunday), 1948; 1951-1954,; 1957 (Oversize 12)
  - Perry Mason by Erie Stanley Garner
    - Proofs (daily)`, Jul 23 1951 -Oct 6 1951; 11 sheets (Oversize 15)
  - Pete the Tramp by C.D. Russell
    - Proofs (daily), 1935 (Oversize 26)
    - Tearsheets (color Sunday), Sep 1935; Nov-Dec 1935,; Jan-Sep 1936,; Nov 1936-Feb 1937,; Apr 1937-Jan 1938 (Oversize 12)
  - Peter Piltdown by Mal Eaton
    - Clippings (color Sunday), 1935-1938 (Oversize 12)
  - Polly and Her Pals by Cliff Sterrett
    - Clippings (color Sunday), 1936 Jan-1937 May; 1937 Sep,; 1937 Nov-1938 Jan; 55 items (Oversize 16)
    - Proofs (daily), 1935-1940 (Oversize 35)
    - Proofs (Sunday), 1934; 1937-1940; includes 2 in color; 191 items (Oversize 23)
  - Priscella's Pop by Al Vermeer